You've arrived, the aquarium.
来ましたね、水族館
Nacchan.
なっちゃん
I guess I'm not that interested in fish.
魚そんなに興味がないんだろう
But there may be a lot of cute fish.
でも可愛い魚いっぱいいるかもね
It's quite long.
ちゃんと長いね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそう そう
Soba is growing.
蕎麦生えてる
You're looking at me.
見入ってるね
What kind of fish do you like?
どんな魚が好き?
Huh?
あれ?
Isn't it huge?
すげーでかくない?
That's good.
あれがいいんだ
I guess that’s what it is, shark?
あれなんだろうね、サメ?
Isn't it a shark?
サメじゃない?
It's probably a shark.
多分サメだよね
In that form.
あの形的に
You might get eaten.
食べられちゃうかもね
That's good.
あれがいいんだ
I like anything big, even animals.
でっかいの好きなのなんでも動物も
Is that so?
そうなの?
I like this.
俺好きだ、これ
My favorite sunfish.
大好きなマンボウ
This is huge.
でっかいよ、これ
Did you know that sunfish are delicious?
マンボウおいしいって知ってた?
That's right.
そうなんだ
They're going to serve something like tuna, right?
マグロみたいなの出すんじゃう?
It looks like he's going to die soon.
すぐ死んじゃうらしいです
Is that so?
そうなの?
As expected of a species.
さすが物種
Also regarding sunfish.
マンボウに関しても
It's cute, and it's big.
可愛いね、でっかくて
Is it over?
終わりかな?
It was beautiful and fun.
綺麗楽しかったな
it was fun.
楽しかった
hey.
ね
Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いですね
You look like a small animal, Hina-chan.
小動物みたいな顔してるね、ひなちゃん
This will be popular.
モテるでしょ、これ
I'm not popular at all.
全然モテない
Aren't you popular?
モテないの?
Don't you choose too much?
選びすぎなんじゃないの?
Aren't you choosing too much?
選びすぎてるんじゃないの?
A man.
男の人
That's right.
そう なんだ
What kind of man do you like?
どういう男の人好きなの?
I like handsome guys.
イケメンが好き
Handsome?
イケメン?
That's right.
そうなんだ
What's wrong with grandpa?
おじいちゃんはダメなの?
Grandpa is no good.
おじいちゃんはダメだ
おじいちゃんはダメなんだ
I like handsome guys.
イケメンが好きなんだよ
As much as possible.
なる べく
You have a cute face.
顔可愛いもんね
It looks good on a handsome guy.
イケメンに似合うもんね
My skin is also pure white.
肌も真っ白じゃん
Don't you play outside?
外だも遊ばないの?
Inside the house.
家の中に
I'm in the house.
家の中にいるんだ
What do you have the most fun doing?
何してるときが一番楽しい?
tell me.
教えて
What are you doing?
何してるとき?
Best when I'm eating.
食べてるときが一番
It's best when I'm eating.
食べてるときが一番いいんだ
What do you like?
何が好きなの?
Sweets.
スイーツ
cute.
可愛い
A cake?
ケーキとか?
What cake do you like?
何ケーキ好きなの?
My favorite cake is Mont Blanc.
ケーキはモンブランが一番好き
Montblanc?
モンブラン?
It's a chestnut one.
栗のやつね
That's delicious.
あれ美味しいよな
Montblanc.
モンブランな
I love you too.
おじさんも好きだよ
I see.
そっか
Don't you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏はいないの?
I'm not there.
いないです
why?
なんで?
Why aren't you here, boyfriend?
なんでいないの、彼氏?
I can't.
できないです
Can't you?
できない?
They just don't make it.
作らないだけだよね
What about Christmas?
クリスマスは?
I eat cake at Christmas.
クリスマスはケーキ食べます
Are you going to eat cake alone?
ケーキ一人食べるの?
That's right.
そうなんだよ
I feel a little lonely.
ちょっと寂しいな
You have such a cute face.
こんな可愛い顔してるね
This will be popular.
モテるぞ、これは
It's the idol side.
アイドル側だよね
Really.
本当にね
I'm told that I'll manage to get to the slope.
なんとか坂にいそうって言われる
It is said.
言われる
Now, stand up for a moment.
じゃあさ、ちょっと立ってみて
Great style.
すごいスタイルいいな
How many centimeters tall?
身長何センチ?
It is 162.
162です
It's 162.
162なんだ
The face is about 150 cm.
なんか顔はさ、150センチくらいのことだよね
It is said.
言われます
There's one in the 60s too.
60にもあるんだ
What about breasts?
おっぱいは?
Is it the size?
サイズですか?
yes.
そう
How many cups?
何カップ?
It's A or B.
AかBです
A or B cup.
AかBカップ
It's called failure.
失敗ってやつだ
It's good to fail.
失敗いいよね
Better than being too big.
デカすぎるよりもね
It's light and convenient.
軽くて便利だ
Is it not on one side?
片っ方にない?
Not at all.
全然ないです
Even if you fail, you're still popular.
失敗でも人気なんだよ
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
My legs are also thin.
足も細いしね
I think it's really cute.
すごい可愛いと思います
What about Kuro-chan?
黒ちゃんどう?
Iina-chan.
いいなちゃん
So cute.
すごい 可愛い
Isn't it cute?
可愛いでしょ?
I'm going to take pictures of a lot of things today, is that okay?
今日いろんなこと撮っちゃうけど大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it so embarrassing?
すごい恥ずかしいんじゃない?
get nervous?
緊張する?
do my best.
頑張る
I'll do my best.
頑張るよ
It makes me nervous.
緊張するよね
Well then, Kuro-chan.
じゃあ黒ちゃん
Should Cardi take it off?
カーディが脱がしちゃおうか
I haven't been playing with guys lately.
最近は男の人と遊んでないんだ
And then I came to this perverted, perverted place.
そしてこの変態な 変態なところに来ちゃって
She really looks like an idol.
本当アイドルみたいだな
Door up.
ドアアップ
How many people have you matched with so far?
今までさ、 何人くらいと一致したことあるの?
About 3 people.
3人くらい
3人くらいか
Are they all good-looking?
全部イケメン?
Yeah.
うん
Don't you act ugly?
ブサイクとやらないの?
Yeah.
うん
What if he was ugly and amazing?
ブサイクですごい人だったら?
He's not handsome.
イケメンじゃないですよ
Still there.
まだそこ
That's because you're really young.
本当に若いからそうだよね
Everyone is like that.
みんなそうだよね
Young children.
若い子はね
Now turn around.
じゃあ後ろを向いてごらん
Isn't your butt quite big?
結 構お尻大きくない?
Yeah.
うん
It's curvy.
プ リプリだね
Are you told?
言われる?
言われるか
Would you like a little more skirt?
もうちょっとスカートなんていい?
Is it okay to wrap it like this in the back?
後ろこうやって巻くっていい?
oh yeah.
そうそう
I can see your pants.
パンツ見えるよ
Is it okay to wrap it from the bottom?
下から巻くっていい?
oh yeah.
そうそう
It was formed under the black color.
黒い下にできたのね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
My butt is being taken so much right now.
今 お尻すごい取られてる
Then look over here.
じゃあこっち向いてごらん
copper?
どう?
Because your butt was taken?
お尻取られたから?
copper?
どう?
Feeling really embarrassed?
いいくらい恥ずかしい感じ?
Well then, Robo-chan.
じゃあロボちゃん
I'll slowly release the button.
ゆっくりボタン外すぞ
It's pure white.
真っ白だね
Your stomach and skin are so beautiful.
お腹もすごい肌きれいね
So please take your time and show me.
じゃあゆっくり見せてごらん
Chikubi is so beautiful.
チクビめちゃめちゃきれい
It's so beautiful.
すごいきれいじゃん
You're a chikubi who doesn't seem to have much experience.
経験少なそうな感じのチクビだね
Properly.
ちゃんと
Look at the colors.
色がほら
So beautiful.
すごいきれい
Let me stand for a moment.
ちょっと立ってもらおう
So beautiful.
すごいきれい
Are you feeling tingly?
チクビツンツンしてる?
Can you touch me?
触られる?
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
Do you like being touched?
チクビ触られるの好き?
usually?
普通?
Have you ever been licked?
舐められたことあるでしょ?
feeling?
気持ち?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
Fran-chan, lower your brush.
フランちゃん、ブラシを下げてみて
What are you going to say?
思いっきりなんて言うの
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
You're being licked.
舐められちゃってるね
Hey, take a look below.
ほら、下見てごらん
Chikubi look.
チクビほら
It's standing really well.
すごい立ってる
Look at the chikubi.
チクビ見てごらん
Fran-chan, do you like chew?
フランちゃん、チュー好き?
Fran-chan has a cute face.
フランちゃん、可愛い顔
Chew lightly.
軽くチュッて
Long
久
Shiburi.
し ぶり
Please chew more.
もっとチューしてね
Hina-chan, please take your tongue out.
ひなちゃん、ベロ出してみて
Please put out your tongue.
ベロ出してね
Try making your own character.
自分からキャラクターしてみて
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Hina-chan is sitting really well.
ひなちゃん、めちゃめちゃ座れてるね
Try sitting for PE.
体育座りしてみて
Please open your legs slowly.
ゆっくり足開いてごらん
You're doing a really naughty pose.
すごいエッチなポーズしてるね
Try making your pants smaller for yourself.
自分でさ、 パンツ細めてごらん
The hair is fine too.
お毛毛もちゃんとあるね
That's not it.
そらないんだ
That's erotic.
エロいね
Look at the pants yourself.
自分でパンツ見てごらん
Just open it.
そのまま開いて
It's so naughty,
すごいエッチだよ、
this.
これ
Well then, just lie down.
じゃあ さ、 そのまま横になってごらん
Hina-chan, lift your legs like this.
ひなちゃん、足こういう意味持ち上げて
Show me everything over there.
あそこ全部見せてごらん
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
Open it with both hands.
開いてね、両手で
Hina-chan is bright pink.
ひなちゃん、真っピンクだね
Look, you can see deep inside.
ほら、奥まで見えるよ
Look here.
こっち見てごらん
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Hina-chan, try touching it.
ひなちゃん、ぐりつんつん触ってみて
Does it feel great?
すごい気持ちいいの?
I'm starting to get a little nervous.
ちょっとビクビクしてきたね
Hina-chan.
ひなちゃん、じゃん
Mainly mancon.
マンコン中心
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
A naughty voice came out.
エッチな声出てきたね
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいい?
where?
どこ?
tell me.
教えて
Does Kurina feel good?
くりな気持ちいい?
Hina-chan, I'm going to go as hard as I can inside Bell's hole.
ひなちゃん、ベルの穴の中思いっきりいっちゃうよ
The deepest place.
一番奥までいるところ
Hina-chan, do you know what's in there?
ひなちゃん、入ってるのわかる?
My pussy is being punched.
マンコン殴られてる
On your feet like this.
足上にこうやって
Make it all.
全部にして
Piledriver.
まんぐりして
Lick it.
それをなめてごらん
Hina-chan, just put one finger in there.
ひなちゃん、そのまま指一本入れてみ
Hina-chan has entered.
ひなちゃん、入っちゃったね
My finger is in the deepest part.
指一番奥まで入ってるよ
Look here.
こっち見て
Does it feel good inside?
中気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Look at the comfortable part above.
上の気持ちいいところしてごらん
It feels good there.
そこ気持ちいいんだ
More together.
もっと一緒に
Yeah.
うん
There are footsteps like that.
そういう足音がある
Yeah.
うん
Please make it feel more comfortable.
もっと気持ちよくしてごらん
Pull it out and make all the holes.
抜 いて穴全部にしてごらん
Go in as hard as you can.
思いっきり入ってごらん
Look here.
こっち見て
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
It's true.
ほんとだ
Hina
ひな
Chan, can I come in like this?
ちゃん、 このまま入るかな?
Can I experiment?
実験していい?
It's thick but will it fit?
太いけど入るかな?
This little pile.
このちっちゃいまんぐり
I entered.
入った
Footsteps below.
下の足音
It's in.
入っちゃったね
It went all the way in.
奥 まで入っちゃったよ
It's gotten that far.
そこまで入っちゃったね
Try to insert your finger all the way inside.
指一番奥まで入ってごらん
The comfortable part above.
上の気持ちいいところ
Hina-chan, does it feel good?
ひなちゃん、気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Feels good
気持ちいい
is.
です
amazing.
すごい
More together.
も っと一緒に
slowly.
ゆっくり
slowly
Please put all your heart into it.
思 いっきり入れてごらん
Shall we go in?
入っちゃう?
Should I go in?
入っちゃうかな?
I put a lot in it.
いっぱい入れた
That's amazing.
すごいね
It came out great.
すごい出ちゃった
A lot came out.
いっぱい出ちゃった
That's amazing.
すごいね
Hina
ひ な
Chan, a lot came out.
ちゃん、 いっぱい出たよ
A lot came out.
すごいいっぱい出たね
Hina-chan came out a lot, but
ひ なちゃん、 いっぱい出たけど、
He came out a lot, but he looked like he was feeling good.
すごいいっぱい出たけど、 気持ちよさそうな顔してたね
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
It was a great color.
すごい色かったよ
Well then, this is it.
じゃあ、次はさ、 これだね
Do you know what's down here?
この下何あるかわかる?
Do you understand?
わかる?
Try saying it.
言ってみて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you too embarrassed to say it?
恥ずかしくて言えない?
So, put your hands on these pants,
じゃあ、このパンツに手をかけて、
Look at it slowly.
ゆっくり見てみ
That embarrassing thing.
その恥ずかしいやつ
Take a seat.
座ってごらん
Look at this.
見てこれ
Just sit still.
つんつん座ってごらん
Hold it tight.
ぎゅっと持ってみ
And move slowly.
で、 ゆっくり動かして
Try increasing it little by little.
ちょっとずつ大きくしてみ
Are you getting bigger?
大きくなってきた?
Bring your face closer to it.
それに顔近づけて
Try smelling that smell.
その匂い嗅いでみて
What does it smell like?
何の匂いする?
The smell of dick?
ちんちんの匂い?
Lick the entire tip.
さきっぽ全部ペロペロ舐めてみ
There are a lot of things that are missing.
落ちんのがいっぱいだね
Then lick everything from the balls to the bottom.
そしたら玉からさ、 下から全部舐めて
Lick it all.
全部舐めて
Lick it all the way to the top.
その上までペロペロ舐めて
Add it all the way to the bottom.
一番奥まで加えてごらん
Make some noise.
一杯音立ててごらん
I got this too.
こっちもってなったね
Could you please add this?
これ加えてもらえない?
Hold it here.
こ っちもって
You've gotten bigger, dick.
大きくなったね、ちんちん
It got bigger.
大 きくなった
Kuro-chan, why don't you sleep there?
黒ちゃん、そこ寝てみ?
Hina-chan, lick it.
ひなちゃん、舐めてみ
Have them lick you a lot.
いっぱいエッチに舐めてもらう
Kuro-chan, do you feel good?
黒ちゃん、気持ちいい?
Because I want to lick everything like that.
そうやって全部舐めてみしたいから
It's about as big as Hina-chan's face, dick.
ひなちゃんの顔ぐらいあるね、ちんちん
It's huge.
でっかいね
Have them all added.
全部加えてもらう
Do you want to try it soon?
早くやってみ?
Use your hands and mouth.
手と口つかって
Is it time to add Kusha?
クーシャーそろそろ入れる?
cute.
かわいい
Hina-chan, can I come in?
ひ な ちゃん、入れるか?
Let me in.
入れよ
Hina-chan, look.
ひなちゃん、見て
Will this kind of penis fit?
こんなおちんちょうきん入るかな?
enter?
入る?
enter.
入る
perhaps?
多分?
I'll come in.
入るよ
My stomach looks tight.
きつそうなお腹です
This guy is slow and slow.
ゆっくりっちぼうこいつ
Yuu
ゆ っ
chestnut.
く り
It hit me in a pinch.
つぼづぼ入っちゃったね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Hina-chan, you made me feel good.
ひ なちゃん、気持ちよくしたんで
This voice came out.
こっちな声出てきたね
It feels good there.
そこ気持ちいいね
Hina-chan, have you ever been cocky?
ひなちゃん、気上したことある?
do not have?
ない?
Shall we try it?
やってみようか
Let's experience it for the first time.
初体験しよう
hey.
ね
Hina-chan, huh?
ひなちゃん、ね
Can I see it once?
一回見ていい?
Hina-chan, would you please put more of your penis in there?
ひなちゃん、ちんちん自分のもっと入れてごらん?
Get on top.
上に乗って
Then slowly move your hips forward and backward like this.
そしたら、 腰をこう前と後ろに ゆっくりこう
Slither.
ずりずりって
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Do you know how far Shibamo is in?
しばもこまで入ってるの分かる?
Look how cute everyone is now.
みんなかわいいの今ほら
I did this.
こんなことしちゃって
hey.
ね
Try shaking harder.
もっと激しく振ってみ
Push me.
押しつけて
Zuri Zuri.
ず りずりって
There was a lot of erotic stuff in there before.
前にいっぱい入ってたエロいの
Just fall forward.
そのまま前に倒れてごらん
Take out your tongue.
ベロ出して
Kuro-chan, please chew.
黒ちゃん、チューして
Kuro-chan, follow me from below.
黒ちゃん、下からついて
I have a lot of tight girls.
きつい女の子いっぱいつきな
From below.
下 から
Hina-chan, take your tongue out.
ひなちゃん、ベロ持って出して
If you fill it up.
いっぱい入れば
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
I watched it.
チ ューしたものだよ
There's a place where it's in.
入ってるところがある
It's hitting me in a lot of places.
ツボツボ刺さってる
Kuro-chan, more.
黒 ちゃん、もっと
Yes, more and more.
そう、もっといっぱいいっぱい
Then.
そしたらさ
Kuro-chan, head over there.
黒ちゃん、頭あっち
Get on the first floor.
1階に乗って
Hina-chan does a really naughty pose.
ひなちゃん、すごいエッチなポーズする
from now.
今から
Ride on top of this like an M.
この上にM字みたいに乗って
Flow this way.
こっち向き流す
Head this way.
こっち向くね
About the back.
手後ろについて
Put chin chin in it.
チンチン入れて
I can see everything.
全部見えるよ
Would you like me to move your butt a little?
お尻ちょっと動かしてもらう?
Kuro-chan, follow me from below.
黒ちゃん、下からついて
Do you want me to shake my hips by myself?
自分で腰を振ってもらう?
About the bottom.
下について
Please make my dick bigger.
チンチンもっと大きくしてあげて
Kuro-chan, from below again.
黒ちゃん、もう一回下から
In four cases.
4つの場合になって
Hina-chan, move your butt yourself.
ひなちゃん、自分でお尻を動かしてさして
You have to hit the deepest spot.
一番奥当てなきゃダメだよ
Do it yourself properly.
自分でちゃんと
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Did you go again?
また行っちゃったの?
That's amazing, Kuro-chan's penis.
すごいね、黒ちゃんのチンチン
Such a cute girl can be accepted three times.
こんな可愛い子3回も受かせられるんだ
Kuro-chan, do you want to come out already?
黒ちゃん、もう出したい?
I want to put it out.
出したい
Finally sleep.
最後に寝て
normal position.
正常位置を
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Kuro-chan, follow me.
黒ちゃん、ついて
Hina-chan, cum in your mouth.
ひなちゃん、口の中出す
It's tiny.
ちっちゃくちゃ
Does your pussy feel good?
マンコ、気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Kuro-chan, cum in your mouth as hard as you can.
黒ちゃん、思いっきり口の中出す
You came out a lot, Kuro-chan.
いっぱい出たね、黒ちゃん
You got me started.
口出されちゃったね
It's full of spirit.
精神まみれだね
Let me see your pussy as it is.
そのままマンコ見せてもらう
I went, pussy.
行った、マンコ
Hey, Kuro-chan, hold your leg over there.
ほら、黒ちゃん、そっち足持って
Spread it out as much as you can.
思いっきり広げて出して
You're still mentally strong.
まだ精神渡れてるね
Kuro-chan, can I get you a tissue?
黒ちゃん、ティッシュ取ってあげる?
There was a really huge amount.
ほんとすごい量出てたね
Was it said for the first time?
初めて口に出された?
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
The face she's wearing right now is so cute.
今、位置してる顔すげえ可愛かったよ
How was your day?
どうだった、今日?
Take it.
取って
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
It was embarrassing, but I did my best.
恥ずかしかったけど、頑張ったね
Yeah, it was embarrassing.
うん、恥ずかしかった
It was so cute.
すごい可愛かったよ
See you again.
また会おうね
thank you.
ありがとう
Bye bye today.
バイ バイ、今日は